But I want to get into one thing right
off the bat.
You were on a podcast and my phone
started blowing up.
And I'm like, "Why is everybody texting
me this? Look what John said about you."
>> What I said?
>> "John is about to get on the podcast."
So Rob, if you have the clip, I want to
start off with this. I want to address
it one by one by one. I want you to
cover this for me. So you're on a
podcast. I don't know which podcast this
is.
Well, whatever it is, I was texted by
everybody with this. So go ahead and
play this clip.
>> I was watching Patrick Bet-David
yesterday and Patrick is a
a hardcore Zionist. He's Iranian. I
don't think he's Jewish. I think he's
like half Assyrian and half Armenian.
>> Yeah.
>> Hang on.
>> But he's a hardcore Zionist and not just
a Zionist, he is a like 1,000%
backer of Reza Pahlavi to return to Iran
and to assume the Peacock Throne and
blah blah blah.
Um
and he was saying yesterday that it's
not 60%
of the Iranian people who support the
overthrow of the regime. It is 94%
>> I don't
>> I don't know when I've ever said that,
but okay, let's keep going.
>> I'm watching you. There are no polls.
>> Hang on. Let's keep going.
>> no polls. You just make this [__] up
to put your your stooge in.
>> The monarchists are crazy online. I mean
>> They are.
>> I I saw some They've been passing around
the message that Iran only became um
Muslim 100 years ago.
>> What?
>> No, that was 1,000 years ago.
>> 1,000 years ago.
>> Yes.
>> And I get that there are still
Zoroastrians and
>> So now watch what happens here, which is
the funniest part.
>> Oh, Elliot Covert, Patrick Bet-David is
Jewish. Okay, I stand corrected. I
wasn't sure.
>> You're not Jewish.
>> No, I'm not Jewish.
>> But I know he's not ethnic Persian. He's
Armenian.
>> there, Rob? Is there anything else that
goes on in the world?
>> Yeah, 94% of his first
>> Curious to know because I want to get
all of it out.
>> Well, that's what they do.
>> fan of you.
>> Literally, I've been asking online like
from these, you You these Persian
monarchists.
>> See, this is what I get for listening to
people in chat. Everybody wants the Shah
back. I find that very hard to believe
considering how brutal the Shah was and
the fact that he was overthrown by his
own people, right? I mean, it wasn't
like he was cooed out by any foreign
power. Quite the op- quite to the
contrary.
So, he
But yeah, they they literally these
these Persian monarchists, they just
they do polls of like the exiles.
>> And you know, okay, you can pause it
right there. Walk me through this.
>> I owe you an apology to you.
>> No, but tell me this. I I'm not I'm not
I I don't want an apology. I I enjoy
talking to you. The last time we spoke I
think out of the seven clips that we
posted, three of them was
upset Jews cuz it was comments you made
that were bad against Massoud and we
played I thought it was very revealing.
I thought it was great.
But walk me through each of these.
Number one, hardcore Zionist, 100%
backer of Pahlavi and then 94%. Tell me.
>> Okay, the reason I said that is because
of Netanyahu's appearance. Number one.
Um and uh
And the comments that you've made about
Pahlavi, like why hasn't this guy called
me back? I want him on the show. Like
why? He's irrelevant?
He's a clown?
>> Why hasn't he called me back? I had him
on the show two times.
>> Yeah, but he when you first invited him
>> Do you know what happened there? He's
asking for help. He cuz the interviewer
the Iranian interviewer that interviewed
me is asking me
are you are you going to help him? Are
you going to help Reza Pahlavi? In In
we're speaking in Farsi and English.
And I said, "No." He asked me for help.
I never heard back from him.
But I made some very bad remarks about
the guy. Have you heard what I've said
about them?
>> No. I'd love to.
>> I don't know how you You must not know
how monarchists think of me right now.
>> No.
>> [laughter]
>> I do you know what? They can't stand me
today. Good.
>> Do you No, no, it's not good. I like
this father. I don't think he's a strong
leader.
>> He's not.
>> He was following me. His wife was
following me. His daughter was following
me. Everybody on followed the
monarchists attacked me because I called
Oh, it's it is in shambles with me in
that relationship. Bro, maybe play clip
>> a that's a badge of honor.
>> if you want to play that.
>> That's a badge of honor.
>> to leave Iran and go camp. By the way,
you know what's the biggest thing that
Iranian people are saying? Hey Reza
Pahlavi, we want you to go to Azerbaijan
and and say a few words from there. Come
closer to Iran. Show some stuff. He's
not doing it. The one thing about Trump,
let me tell you what was very crystal
clear about Trump, about Milei, about
Bukele. You know what it was? They're
willing to do the legwork. They're
willing to go out there. They're willing
to pay the a price. They're willing to
drive. They're willing to work their
tails off.
It's very obvious. We the markets said,
"Who is this crazy Elvis-looking guy
from Argentina? There's no way he'll
ever win making out with people on
stage." Guess what? He won. Who is this
Bukele guy that's in his early mid-30s?
And by the way, let me give you what's
going to be confusing. I have a painting
of his dad at my house.
>> [laughter]
>> So, I'm a fan of his father.
So, this is this is not like a bash
towards
the family.
>> No, of course.
>> And so, but this is towards I was
critical of him because for 47 years
he's been talking about he wants to have
Iran be free and he didn't do it. And
And keep in mind, a part of me is Yeah,
that's the painting in my house. That's
a 15-ft painting. His father's right in
the middle. My criticism is of him.
But I was watching, you know, I'm like,
"Why Did somebody tell you I'm a
Zionist? Did you Who's that?"
>> It was in the It was in the chat.
>> No, no, but did
>> I was reading the chat.
>> Did any other influencers that you go
and do interviews with? Did anybody
whisper to you off camera, "Hey, be
careful with Patrick. He's a Zionist."
>> Yes.
>> Who was that?
>> Oh, I I don't want to out him like that,
but he said, "Oh, you're going on PBD?"
I said, "Yeah." He said, "Be careful.
Patrick comes out swinging on Israel."
>> Is this a big name?
>> Yeah, it's pretty big name.
>> One of the biggest names?
So, then I know who it is.
>> I don't want to I don't want to out
>> Was his family in the CIA before, maybe?
>> I I'm I I've got to stop.
>> Okay.
>> But but I but I want to apologize on the
record because I was wrong.
>> Okay. So, so that and and the and the uh
the BB side because you know who's the
only person in the world that
interviewed BB and Nick Fuentes within
30 days?
>> It's got to be you.
>> It's only me.
>> It's got to be.
>> You So, you know what the problem is
with me, John? This is the problem.
The same people that want freedom of
speech, that pitch it,
>> Yeah.
>> don't practice it.
>> What do I mean by that? They generally
want to only talk to people that agree
with them.
>> Yes. It's the exact
>> You and I don't agree on maybe a few
things. No, which is why I so enjoyed
the conversation. I love the
conversation because
the my my thoughts are Alicia, just
bring it to me. It's totally fine. My
thoughts are it's like man, I I don't
know. He He's a CI guy. He must know
more than I do. He has some experience.
I want to know. But,
>> No, I'm I'm wrong and I apologize.
>> go to the other one cuz I want to clear
all of this up. Let's go to the one
about when you said 94%. I'd love to
know when I said 94% Rob, can you take
one of the language learning models?
Matter of fact, why don't we do both of
them. Take uh take chat GPT and do Grok
and ask a question, how do you want to
pose this question? What percentage of
Iranians don't support the IRGC?
What percentage of Iranians don't
support
the IRGC?
Okay, ask the same exact question.
So, what we'll typically do is we'll ask
different and we'll go do our own and
then we'll look at the numbers that's
being given. Okay.
>> Wow.
>> This is which one? What does it say?
Around 80 to 92% of Iranians appear to
not support the IRGC
based on available polls, support they
likely don't the direct polling on the
IRGC challenge and due to Iran
repression, surveillance, and
self-censorship. Okay, great. Leaked
internal Iranian government poll 2025
commissioned by the presidency. A
confidential report found 92% of
Iranians hate the regime.
And that's from Yahoo explicitly
including supreme leader Khamenei and
the IRGC, not just specific officials or
policies.
This was cited by Iranian experts and
aligns with widespread dissatisfaction.
Gamin is the one that I saw. By the way,
I haven't even seen the one above that
we're reading for the
Go to the Gamin one. Gamin says what?
Independent arts online poll 10,000 13
to 14 have confidence in the IRGC. So
that leaves another 86.
And what does it say? Broader regime
rejection. Only about 15 to 20% want
Islamic Republic to continue. 70 to 80%
favor regime change transformation. High
agreement 70% with designating the IRGC
as a terrorist organization in Iran. Can
you go to the Is this uh Chat GPT or
Grok?
>> That was Grok.
>> see what Chat GPT says. Zoom in a little
bit.
Okay, so direct IRGC split 2019 Maryland
poll 80%.
Uh Maryland Iran poll So that's
Maryland. So you can criticize that
because that's from here. 80%. Gamin is
the same one. I think Gamin is from
Netherlands. 71% of Iranians oppose.
20% support. So you see what numbers
were repeating. We're repeating reports
that are coming in. So it's not a
>> You're You're right and I'm wrong and I
apologize.
>> No, I I appreciate that. And the And the
last one I want to show you, which is
crazy, to get this out of the way so we
can have our
uh
conversation, is do you know who I
brought on the podcast who never agreed
to go on the podcast with anybody? And
when he came in,
he was the most suspicious guy here
looking at me saying, "Why do you have
me on the podcast?" You know who it was?
>> No, who's that?
>> of IRGC.
>> No.
>> That guy right there. Mohsen Sazegara.
Okay?
Do you know who he was?
>> miss that?
>> So check this out. I'm going to I'm
going to show this for you. So if you go
a little bit lower to see who is He's
the founder of Go a little bit lower.
Put IRGC arrest blah blah blah blah
blah.
Can we find the IRGC there with him and
Khomeini?
Uh Okay, right there in the middle.
>> There he is.
>> An Iranian journalist and political He
was the founder of the Islamic
Revolutionary Guard
Corps after the Iranian Revolution. He
was the guy It was between him and
Khomeini that started the IRGC. He would
do the intro to all the tapes
where they would send in for Iranians to
listen before the revolution happened to
pin
Pahlavi's people against him. This was
the voice. Then you had Khomeini. I had
him on the podcast. And the claim was
that SAVAK killed 100,000 people. Now,
keep in mind, he's the propaganda guy
that that said SAVAK, which is, you
know,
uh uh Pahlavi's CIA, Pahlavi's Mossad,
right?
>> At the end of the podcast, I wanted to
ask him,
"It's been 40-something years now. You
were involved. Was it a lie that Shah
killed 100,000 people?"
This is not a fan of me. This is not a
Shah a fan of the Pahlavi. He did not
come in knowing what we were going to
talk about. Look at his answer here. Go
ahead, Rob.
>> Compared Shah with Khomeini,
let me say judgment now
that many documents have come out
you know, for instance, on those days
opposition claimed that 100,000
political prisoners Shah has.
Uh there are 100,000 political prisoners
in Iran.
>> That was false.
It was only 3,000.
>> 3,500.
>> 3,000 uh
few hundred.
>> Right.
>> Uh
Now that if I compare
Shah with Khomeini, definitely I
I already said. First of all, his
personality, Shah,
was a better guy than Khomeini.
First. Second,
uh
his
what he did for Iran
because that he believed in you know,
modernization of Iran
was definitely better than Islamic
Republic. As I said
>> You can pause. I would suggest if you
want to watch it, watch it. It's
fascinating cuz it's a little
background. I'll text it to you.
I think you'll enjoy it, but
these are my positions. My concern is,
John, people that I've had good
relationships. There's this one guy that
I think he's the head of the snake
that behind closed doors is creating
division and creating rumors and stories
about and he's a very influential guy.
Could be the same guy that told you
stuff about me. Very heavy-weight guy.
Very, very heavy-weight guy. I think
we're talking about the same person. If
I tell you I've heard 10 people that he
said stuff about me behind closed doors,
that's a small number.
>> Wow.
>> So, this keeps coming back to me. I'm
like, what is his issue? What is his
challenge? We won't talk about the name
cuz I don't want you to be in an
uncomfortable position. I'm not going to
push that topic. All I'm saying is I
wanted to make sure I presented this to
you
>> and any pushback you have, please go for
it. I'm all ears.
>> No, no. I owe you an apology. I said
you've you've shown me wrong and I I'm
sorry that I uh
perpetuated an untruth. Hi, everybody.
I'm John Kiriakou, former CIA officer.
Please find me on Minnect. We have a lot
to talk about. CIA, FBI, DOD, torture,
secret prisons, international
renditions. Maybe you or your child want
to apply for a job at the CIA and are
looking for some tips. Let me know.
There's a lot we can talk about. You
pick the subject, we'll make it happen.
Again, it's on Minnect. Thanks and I'll
see you soon.
>> If you enjoyed this video, you want to
watch more videos like this, click here.
And if you want to watch the entire
podcast, click here.